SAVON HUYNH

xqhuynh@gmail.com	612-386-7919	Lino Lakes, MN 55014
Portfolio Site	<u>LinkedIn</u>	<u>GitHub</u>

BIO

Educated and hardworking military veteran who loves to use technology to solve problems. My expertise lies within front-end web apps but I'm also capable of working on the backend. I'm a lifelong learner (currently studying C#) and I love to try new things.

SKILLS

- React
- Node.js
- Express.js
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL

- Git & GitHub
- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- Redux

- Material UI
- jQuery
- Bootstrap
- Ajax

WORK HISTORY

Software Engineer Student, Prime Digital Academy

March 2022 - Present

Minneapolis, MN

Solo Project: Sweet Surrender eCommerce Store

- Design wireframes using Figma and translate prototype to website design
- Create eCommerce web application using PERN stack in addition to Material UI, Passport, and Bootstrap within 2-week sprint

Client Project: Groupie Web Application

- Engage with client and provide prototype based on client specifications using Figma and present to client for approval
- Design web application within 2-week sprint utilizing PERN stack along with Amazon AWS,
 Google Maps and Google Places 3rd party API
- Present web application to client and other stakeholders after completion

Auto Body Estimator, Master Collision

October 2021 – March 2022

Minneapolis, MN

- Oversaw auto repairs from conception to completion utilizing various estimating and part sourcing software
- Developed store strategies to raise client pool, expand store traffic, and optimize profitability
- Communicated with all stakeholders through the repair process and set firm timelines for repair completion

Federal Grants IT Intern, U.S. Dept of Health and Human Services September 2021 – December 2022 Remote

- Assisted in the development of usable, accessible interfaces for HHS grants.gov website which allows for a streamlined grants management process
- Contributed to and maintained HHS grants GitHub repository

Ramp Agent, Delta Airlines

March 2020 - October 2021

Minneapolis, MN

- Prepared, coordinated, and communicated with other departments for aircraft departure and arrival in a safe and timely manner in a fast-paced environment
- Cross-trained and contributed to the overall success of ramp operations

Auto Body Estimator, Friendly Chevrolet

March 2019 - January 2020

Fridley, MN

- Compiled auto damage estimates for insurance companies and clients using estimating software and technology
- Communicated repair expectations: plan, monitor, evaluate, and review job orders

Customer Service Manager, Abra Auto Body

January 2018 – September 2018

Roseville, MN

- Conducted daily meetings with technicians and estimators regarding daily goals and expectations
- Initiated and oversaw auto repairs for clients and insurance companies
- Contributed to the revenue growth of the shop to become the top two earners in the state

Service Center Estimator, Progressive Insurance

July 2015 - January 2018

Burnsville, MN

- Utilized estimating and repair management software to determine damage quotes and assess repairability
- Streamlined the repair process with auto body shops thus cutting costs while increasing client satisfaction

Console Operator, United States Navy

January 2011 – January 2015

Norfolk, VA

- Supervised and trained crew members in the safe and efficient transport of over 1.3 million gallons of jet fuel
- Ensured the safe transport of jet fuel during refueling-at-sea and flight operations while maintaining speed and accuracy
- Trained and onboarded over 500 incoming sailors and scheduled onboarding events and activities

EDUCATION

Full Stack Engineer, Prime Digital Academy

August 2022

Certificate of Completion

Minneapolis, MN

Information Technology Management, University of Minnesota

December 2021

Bachelor of Science

Minneapolis, MN